Chris Dekker

Software Engineer

Profile

I'm a hard-working developer who has been in many development positions. Because of this, I'm able to quickly switch into any development role required and am able to use my prior knowledge to solve problems effectively.

I work on personal projects and learning new things in my spare time.

As I'm currently applying for a remote position, I'd like to note that I am willing to travel on occasion.

Employment History

Software Engineer II at Newfold Digital, Burlington (US)

(Working through AppMachine (Leeuwarden, NL) – sub company)

August 2020 — Current

- Worked on core products such as WordPress plugins and themes.
- Consistently communicated in a lucid and effective manner.
- Participated in staff and team meetings and offered a positive presence and outlook.
- Worked with a high level of confidence and ambition.
- Daily problem solving.

DevOps Engineer at iWink, Groningen

February 2020 — August 2020

- Consistently communicated in a lucid and effective manner.
- Participated in staff and team meetings and offered a positive presence and outlook.
- Worked with a high level of confidence and ambition.
- Worked on new server setups and solving problems.
- Collaborated with the IT Team to ensure that security software was properly installed on all employee computers.

Full-stack Developer at Jobs & Media Group, Groningen

June 2018 — February 2020

- Brought forth in-depth industry knowledge and experience.
- Investigated and reported cybercrime.
- Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications.
- Worked to solve complex problems using the latest in Cloud, Mobile, and Web Technologies.
- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.

Back-end Developer at Social Brothers, Utrecht

April 2017 — June 2018

- Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.
- Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications.
- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.

Details

Leeuwarden, The Netherlands +31616021710

dekkercw@gmail.com

Date of birth

May 1st, 1997

Nationality

Dutch

Links

LinkedIn

My Company

Skills

Docker

Laravel Framework

WordPress

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

AJAX

jQuery

React.js

React Native

SCSS/SASS

HAProxy

Git

Jenkins

Bash

Vim

Languages

English (Professional)

Dutch (Mother Tongue)

Hobbies

Technology, music (all kinds), airsoft (sport) and travelling.

IT Specialist at Student aan Huis, The Netherlands

June 2016 — May 2017

- Consistently communicated in a lucid and effective manner.
- Worked to represent the company in a positive and enthusiastic manner.
- Brought forth passion and enthusiasm, resulting in favourable outcomes.
- Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.

IT Intern at De Nederlandsche Bank, Amsterdam

(The central bank of the Netherlands)

January 2015 — May 2015

- Brought forth the ability to work well independently and also with others.
- Followed directions and multitasked well.
- Remained positive and hopeful even in stressful situations.
- Handled incoming and outgoing mail.
- Provided office employees with continual support.

Education

MBO4 (Associate's degree) - Application Development, LOI (independent study), Groningen

July 2016 — July 2018

Diploma: no

This study is meant to finish the study I started at ROC. It covers the same information but as it is an independent study, I was able to go through it all at a faster pace.

MBO4 (Associate's degree) - Application & Media Development, ROC, Utrecht

February 2015 — February 2016

Diploma: no

Learning the basics of web development using technologies such as PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML. I also learned more about database management, application management and application deployment.

MBO3 (Associate's degree) - IT Management, MBO College, Hilversum

June 2013 — July 2015

Diploma: no

I learned the basics of computer management and assembly/disassembly of computer systems (e.g. servers, towers etc.). This study also included an in-depth course on computer networking (CISCO CCNA).

VMBO-GL (High School Diploma), Wellant College, Naarden

June 2009 — July 2013

Diploma: yes